scholar360.com 2014-02-09

# Edvance360 - Terms of Service

**Welcome to Edvance360. Please review the Privacy Policy.**

Thank you for your interest in Edvance360. This privacy policy applies to public, outward facing, home Website: www.Edvance360.com. It does not apply to any Edvance360 products.   
**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site or fill out a form on our site.   
When requesting a demo or requesting information from us, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number.   
**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
  * To send periodic emails
  * The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.   
**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information   
We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits.   
**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.   
**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.   
**Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), our policy is located at <http://www.edvance360.com/privacy_policy.php>.   
**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.   
**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at [http://www.edvance360.com](http://www.edvance360.com/).   
**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.   
**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.   
This policy was last modified on 1/25/2013.   
**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.   
http://www.edvance360.com 2133 Upton Drive, Suite 216-206 Virginia Beach, VA 23454 USA support@Edvance360.com
